Oh, hey!
Just in time.
I was getting some stuff, out of the way.
So that I can share with you.
How to give a hot oil treatment.
Now if you're not already doing this at home, this is something that you might want to try.
It's excellent for moisture and shine.
Now, what kind of oil are you going to use?
There's several kinds out there.
Find something that works best for you.
You can use avocado oil, peanut oil, baby oil, olive oil.
Ovee, as some like to say.
But listen, whatever type of oil, you like to use.
Make sure you preheat it, in a microwave.
Don't make it too hot.
Because we are applying it, directly to the scalp.
Remember, as you apply oil.
It will get on the hair.
So cover your head with a plastic cap.
And remember, keep it on for fifteen to twenty minutes.
If you choose, go ahead and heat a towel.
Place that on your head, as well.
This will help to open up the cuticle and allow that moisture and oil to get deep down, inside.
Last but not least, remember rinse very well.
Shampoo first but rinse very well.
Follow up with leavening or a rinsing conditioning.
Thanks for watching.
My name is Sylvia Russell.
And this is how, you can do a hot oil treatment.